Don't worry, we'll wait on you, Kelsey.
All right, ready to roll. All right. Uh,
obviously we uh, you know, the weekend
is not complete, but we've got a little
bit of a break or really a long break
here before um, you know, our last pick
and then the undrafted free agency
process. Um, we're really pleased with
at least where we sit. Um, you know, as
we head into the sixth round, um, you
know, we expect by the end of the
weekend, we'll be able to add, you know,
10 rookies that we're really excited
about. Um, as well as, you know, two
future fourth round picks in the 27
draft. you know, at the onset of this or
I guess you know, uh, last week I talked
about, you know, our goal heading into
the weekend is, you know, not just the
first round, but it's how do we maximize
the resources that we head into the
draft with, and that's whether, you
know, you're using those resources, some
of them for veteran players, whether
you're using it to generate more by
trading down, obviously the players that
you select, um, and then the future
draft capital that you're able to to
manufacture. So, we're really pleased
with where we sit today with the
combination of of players and future
assets that we're able to create. Um,
you know, we're looking forward to
finishing strong and um signing some
undrafted free agents that um you know,
can help our club this year. So, with
that, I'll open up for questions.
>> Drafting Jaylen Green and just what your
thinking behind him and what traits did
you like about him?
>> Yeah, it was it's probably a little
similar to what I mentioned yesterday,
Mary Kay, where you know, at the
quarterback position, it's the most
important sports. you know, we'll we'll
we'll make a bet or acquire a player
that we like if it's the right cost. Um
with Talon specifically, uh very mature
young man. Um really strong makeup and
he has rare physical gifts. Um he has
size, he has elite speed. Um he has a
big arm. Um you know, he's going to need
some polish with this game. Uh but he
has the work ethic and he has the acumen
to do so. So um we're looking forward to
adding him to the roster and adding him
to the mix in terms of competition.
Let's talk about potentially moving
Talon to wide receiver tight end.
>> We're not. He's playing quarterback.
He's playing quarterback.
>> Andrew, when you talk, you talk about,
you know, polishing the turnovers were
obviously the big thing about his game
that seemed to be a red flag when he was
at Arkansas.
When you watched him on film, how much
of I mean, do you see a pathway to where
he can work on that as he develops at at
this level? Yeah, I I think context is
important with that type of thing,
Chris. You know, I think um you know,
Arkansas, they were actually one of the
the better off in college football and
faced I think it was like the toughest
slate of of college football opponents.
Um you know, with um you know, the other
side of the ball was was not nearly as
productive, you know, to put it to put
it kindly. And so I think as we've seen
here when there's maybe a little bit of
undue stress towards one side of the
ball it can put you in disadvantageous
situations and I think Talon had a fair
amount of that. That being said there
are absolutely areas of his game that he
has to that he has to clean up. Um but
we are looking forward to working with
him and and potentially developing him
uh because he does have a really strong
makeup rare physical gifts and then
gifts and then really the want to to
improve.
you when you pick a quarterback like
this with this much just raw skill even
if he's not ready to start or play for
you, can you find a way to use that guy
as a weapon?
>> Yeah. No, that's a good question and I
think um so the short answer is yes. Um
obviously his gift as a ball carrier and
a runner is is pretty unique. Um, but it
does have to go within the whole um,
you know, I guess it really has to go
with the offensive vision and I think
that that's something that over the
course of the spring and into training
camp um, as our offensive staff works
with, you know, this group of players
um, you know, we'll define that identity
and figure out how much of that, you
know, we could incorporate, we could
potentially incorporate.
>> It doesn't. Yeah, it doesn't it doesn't
mean anything work with all those guys
and um we like
>> compare like Taylor
Jackson, but obviously knowing that Todd
has worked with like a really dynamic
quarterback, how much that maybe uh gave
you a little more comfort in making the
pick, though you acknowledge he's going
to need some polish.
>> Honestly, Daniel, it it had very little
to do with that. Um Todd's worked with
obviously he's worked with Lamar, but
Lamar was pretty unique relative to the
quarterbacks that he had worked with
previously. Um, I don't know that Lamar
and Stson Bennett could be more polar
opposite. Um, that's one of Todd's
gifts, the ability to maximize, you
know, offensive offensive skill sets
period. And particularly at that, you
know, at that spot. Um, you know, for us
it was as we looked at the prospects who
were available to us. Um, you know,
their relative strengths and weaknesses.
Um, you know, we felt like Talm was the
right pick at the top of six. Um, and,
um, you know, look, we we're we're
excited to work with them.
You guys have typically had four
quarterbacks at least in the offse and
throughout training camp. Like what's
what's the benefits for many?
>> Yeah. Well, part of it you needed to get
through. I mean, look, we we lived it
firsthand last year, right? Like you
needed to get through to get through
camp. You know, we do believe in
keeping, you know, three on the active
roster and ideally a fourth on the
practice squad. Um but it's um you know,
it's an important position. there is um
you know attrition throughout the year.
Um and I think also you know the the
other element is
it's never a problem to have too many
good players. You know it just it just
isn't like even as I think through last
year with that position um you know we
had two young guys you know two vets who
you know either got hurt or um you at
one point were were no longer the
starter because of performance. um and
we were able to turn those, you know,
those players into to resources that
could help the team, you know, this
upcoming off seasonason. So, um
sometimes it's not a linear path in
terms of how they positively impact, you
know, the the roster of the
organization. It may not always be on
field. Um but, you know, we're going to
try and make as many, you know,
calculated bets as we can and um you
know, take steps from there. Andrew, um,
going back to Duke Kalin, the offense he
played in at at Arkansas, Bobby Petrino,
also, you know, kind of off of Daniel
with with Lamar. I mean, what does that
offense do specifically to kind of help
a quarterback prepare a quarterback to
kind of go I mean, can he is there
things that transfer from? I
>> I I I mean, I think there are a lot of
commonalities in college and pro
offenses. Um, you know, maybe I should
back up. There's only one Lamar Jackson,
you know, and so I understand the
comparison there, but there's one Lamar
Jackson. Um, you know, I think
I think how Arkansas deployed Talon and
the run game, the QB driven run game,
you know, that's probably like the the
bigger, you know, the bigger component,
the, you know, the bigger similarity.
And, um, when you have someone with his
athletic gifts, you know, that's
something that you certainly want to
utilize within the offensive system.
>> I guess when you following up, I mean, I
guess it was more about what how Patrino
prepares quarterbacks more so than a
direct comparison to to Lamar.
>> Yeah, I mean like you know his his his
track record speaks for itself. Um you
know that being said, you know, all
these quarterbacks who come into the
NFL, you know, this weekend they have a
lot to learn and fortunately we have one
of the best, you know, one of the best
teachers with, you know, with Todd and
we know he's in good hands.
>> 37 turnovers.
>> Sorry.
>> How do you get past just the 37
turnovers in two two seasons?
>> Yeah. So, I think that goes with with
context, right? Like, um, you know, part
of it is, you know, is it a situation
where they're where they're down,
they're in heavy dropback, their passing
scores, and then part of it is like,
yeah, guys do need to take steps and
improve, Tony. Um, but the other side of
the coin is, you know, you do have, you
know, players who are able to generate
enough of enough explosive plays where
um a not a terminal, but like maybe a
higher turnover rate is um at least more
doable for the team. And that's what
Arkansas, you know, experienced. You
know, probably a perfect example would
be maybe, you know, Josh Allen earlier
in his career um where he made so many
explosive plays that you could live with
some of the errors. Now, once he became
an MVP, he was able to minimize those
with with time on task and experience,
but um you know, at this point in the
draft, there there are no perfect
prospects, but um you know, Tailon has
that make us want to work with them.
>> It's a two-part question. Um, if
Bradford could beat out could win a
center job,
>> would that be ideal for you? And we need
to move Jams to right guard.
>> I would say the thing that would be
ideal is just to have the best five out
there. Like I don't I don't I don't
really care who it is, you know, as long
as we have quality production at all
five spots.
>> That would happen. The second part would
be having two rookies starting. Would
that be uh a little bit dicey?
>> I don't think so. I mean, the Patriots
had that and went on to the Super Bowl
this year.
>> Like about Joe Blair and
what I guess what's his outlook as he
know comes in as far as
>> Yeah, Joe has size. Um really good
hands. Um he is a player that can
produce both in the Y, which is kind of
your traditional inline, you know, role,
and the F role, which is a little bit
more of a receiving role. Um so to have
that flexibility in the room um is
helpful and important. Uh so he was a
guy that we liked. We felt was you know
there for the value and um you know
we're happy to add him to the team.
>> Go to make all four of those picks that
were so close together.
>> Uh we were ready to. I was hoping that
we wouldn't have to just because I
thought that look there were players
that we like there. Um but I thought
combination of some of the things that
we did were going to be more impactful
for the team.
When you look at the the versatility so
many of these guys that you guys have
been drafted have, how much do you
anticipate that maybe playing into camp
as they get here of exploring other ways
that they might be used outside of their
primary role? Yeah, it's a um it's
actually honestly a little bit of a
delicate balance like you know Todd
talks about it all the time and um he's
used some other young players that he's
coached where the excitement can be
while like you know when we collect this
guy he can do this, he can do that, he
can do this and you don't want to spread
that too thin through early. So you know
we'll probably um you know start them
off in in let them get their seal so to
speak before you know branching out. Um
but it it's certainly something that
we're excited about as we move forward.
seen combine results from a guy that
size in terms of tail since like Calvin
Johnson. What is it that that point in
the draft just the athleticism just
outweighs like maybe a more polished
passer like a ner in that situation?
>> Yeah, you know, I wouldn't necessarily
compare him to the other prospects other
than say that we felt like Talon's
makeup um you know, his physical we just
think there's a lot to work with.
>> Yeah.
I know obviously you guys don't have an
answer from Joel on in terms of his
future, but given the amount of
resources dedicated to the offensive
line that you guys have have obviously
done, is is there any thing to read into
there? I guess in terms of you guys in
terms of like maybe with the direction
you guys are heading as as far as the
offensive line is concerned,
>> I wouldn't say so. I think when we've
been at our best, when we had, you know,
when we had the best unit in the league,
um we were deep. It wasn't just quality,
but it was it was depth as well. And so,
um, you know, there are a couple
positions that once you get past this
time of the year, you just can't acquire
till like really the next off season.
Um, and then the offensive line position
group, that's one of those spots. So,
when we can add players, you know, the
bigger guys that that are hard to find,
you know, we'll do that.
>> Parker, when you drafting it, I think
you said something like you're he's
exactly what you're looking for. um what
is it about him and is the weight and
concern?
>> Yeah, you know, we always, you know, and
and Hops even probably best at saying
this, like, you know, if you didn't
know, you wouldn't be able to tell with
his, you know, with his play. Um, but
really the bigger thing is, and you
could see it when we had um when we had
JC here, when we had Nick Harris when he
was healthy, and then in Baltimore when
they had, you know, Tyler Linderbomb,
um, the centers that that can pull and
work at the second level and get to the
perimeter because of their athleticism
and speed, they they give you a lot of
optionality in the run game. And that's
something that Parker does very very
well. So, we're excited about um, you
know, that part of his profile.
you talk about maybe the makeup of your
quarterback room right now obviously two
really young guys three now really young
guys two that have some experience and
then just overall the just the makeup
the energy of the room
>> yeah I I mean I think the three guys
that we've had here have worked really
hard and they've got along really well
um we've been really pleased with the
you know early part of the offseason
program and we think you know TM will
really fit in nicely because of how he's
wired his work ethic Um, you know, so
we're we're looking forward to seeing
that group progress over the course of
the spring and summer.
>> Do you feel like Deshan
I know he was a really good mentor to
the younger guys last year and
everything. Do you think he'll be good
for someone like like Ton with his Pro
Bowl background and all of that?
>> Yeah, like Deshawn's Deshan's great with
his teammates. Um, and and I I'd imagine
that would continue to be the case. Um,
that group they they work together
really well and they get along really
well
>> this stage of the draft. How much does a
guy and sort of in relation to to Justin
Jefferson, how much does a guy having
that special teams quality and that as a
characteristic in their game maybe like
boost them on your board or sort of fit
into the picture when you're thinking
about value at at this at this stage?
>> It's definitely a factor. Um it's not a
one-sizefits-all approach. You know, I
think with with Justin, he's a a DNA
match for this defense because, you
know, we'll prioritize speed, range,
athleticism, and sacrifice a little bit
of how we play. Um, but then also like
his ability in in the kicking game is is
certainly a bonus um because it gives a
relatively high floor for his year one
role.
>> Right into the season that the offseason
is going to be mostly about the offense,
right? The resources. I'm just wondering
when you were interviewing Todd and
talking to Todd before he got the job,
how much of that was a discussion topic
on how you're going to fix it and
exactly how he thought you might be able
to fix?
>> Yeah, we were transparent with all the
candidates we talked to about that part
of it. You know, we were honest with
where we were in our, you know, our
roster life cycle and said, "Hey, look
here, here's how we've positioned
ourselves, you know, going into this
year and how here's how we generally uh
anticipate deploying the assets." So,
that's something that we were very open
at. I think to accept a job, you know,
this big as like a, you know, head coach
in the NFL, um, you know, when you're
walking to a team with transition, like
you have to have visibility in terms of,
you know, what, you know, what that'll
look like moving forward.
>> Andrew, you had not drafted, but you had
some a group of players in for for
tryyouts during the voluntary mini camp.
Are you planning on are you planning on
keeping some around continuing those
tryyouts signing any of them? Have any
decisions?
>> Uh we have not any today. Um you know
that's probably TBD anticipate that
we're signing any veterans in the short
term. But you know it's something that
we could revisit as we get through draft
week and as we get through the um
undrafted free agent signing process.
>> Taylor Green complete the quarterback
room.
>> Uh yes. Uh you know what? Let me back
up. I should I've I should have learned
the I I've learned the hard way not to
say anything definitively.
The current plan is that we would roll
with those four. I can't predict if
something else comes up. So yes, that
would be the intention.
>> He has started so many games and college
has been around for a long time. He's
played a lot of football. How did that
maybe sort of factor into your decision?
you know, it's part of the equation,
Mary Kay, but I wouldn't say that it
was, you know, by any means like the
heaviest weight or the driving force,
you know, behind the decision. Um, but
yeah, it it it does it does play a role
in
>> feel like you construct like through the
draft, through the offse, construct this
offensive line to make it conducive to a
Joel returns
to come back.
>> Uh, I put it this way, we'll never run
away from good players. of all your
picks, which is the most surprising you
you got?
>> That's a great question, Jeff.
>> Um, honestly, it it's it's E-Man. Like,
it it really it's Emanuel. Um,
that's the one that I I wouldn't have
anticipated that he would have been
available where where we selected him.
>> So much about quarterback. So, when you
entered this weekend, did you think you
were going to take Taylor? Like, was
that part of the plan? I mean, I know I
know things changed, but like when you
envisioned it, was that
>> I'd say this like there was um
I don't know that you can predict day
three of the draft. Um we knew that
quarterback could have be one of the
positions as we thought through how day
three could play out that we could make
a selection. Um and he was certainly in
the pool of quarterbacks that obviously
he was in the pool of quarterbacks that
um could come in consideration depending
on how the board felt. But I I wouldn't
say it was like, okay, hey, look, you
can't be so strict with your planning
because you just you don't you don't
control how the names come off the come
off the board.
>> All right. Thanks a lot.
>> Yep.